<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ABlazingEBoy&#39;s Archive</title>
    <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ABlazingEBoy&#39;s Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© ablazingeboy {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 22:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ablazingeboy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pop-Tart Reviews from 2021: A Strange Smorgasbord of Storebought Sweets</title>
      <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/poptarts2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/poptarts2021/</guid>
      <description>Preface Reading this, you may find it quite odd that I&amp;rsquo;m writing reviews about pop-tarts of all things, but then again if you know me it might make a little more sense. That being said, hear me out. The origin of this series of reviews is a story that starts around 11 months ago from the writing of this post, in late March of 2021.
At the time, my life was very different than it is now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Log: Numpet</title>
      <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/numpet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:37:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/numpet/</guid>
      <description>Description The Numpet is a 4-button &amp;ldquo;macropad&amp;rdquo; that uses binary to replicate the featureset of a full number pad. This is accomplished by having each key combination read as a binary number, which then is converted into it&amp;rsquo;s decimal counterpart and sent to the computer as a keyboard input (e. g. Pressing the 1st and 4th button represents 1001 in binary, translating to the number 9). As 4 buttons can represent up to the number 15 in binary, numbers 1-9 output numbers 1-9, number 10 outputs 0 (this is to account for the fact that 0000 is the resting state of the device), and numbers 11-15 represent other functions such as Enter and Backspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Thoughts on the Sunsetting of TeenagersGaming</title>
      <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/tgshutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 13:14:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/tgshutdown/</guid>
      <description>Written on December 30th, 2021
This post consists of my thoughts and my thoughts only on this matter. No other mods were involved in the writing of this post. In addition, please be decent human beings. Do not go out and harass any mod, TG or otherwise. Many of them are my friends and none of them had any knowledge of this or input on it. Thank you.
In addition, check out Cheese_Addict&amp;rsquo;s transparency document here, as it provides a more general overview of the whole ordeal, and this article assumes you&amp;rsquo;ve read that and references screenshots from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Review: Five Star Strong Cold Brew</title>
      <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/fivestarstrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 23:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/fivestarstrong/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write a coffee review. I have zero qualification to do so, but the fact that my blood is 75% caffeine helps.
This is going to be the first of a series of reviews on the odd coffee beverages I consume to summon enough energy to get through the workday. The subject of this review is Five Star Strong Vanilla Cold Brew.
I picked this up from my local grocery store this morning, after seeing it around for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Blog</title>
      <link>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/i-made-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:36:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ablazingeboy.github.io/blog/i-made-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>Yeah I made a blog. What are you going to do about it?
It&amp;rsquo;s in light mode. Why? Because it is.
Deal with it.
-eboy &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
