<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on I Need More Coffee</title>
    <link>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on I Need More Coffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© ablazingeboy {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 13:14:04 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Thoughts on the Sunsetting of TeenagersGaming</title>
      <link>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/tgshutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 13:14:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/tgshutdown/</guid>
      <description>Written on December 30th, 2021
This post consists of my thoughts and my thoughts only on this matter. No other mods were involved in the writing of this post. In addition, please be decent human beings. Do not go out and harass any mod, TG or otherwise. Many of them are my friends and none of them had any knowledge of this or input on it. Thank you.
In addition, check out Cheese_Addict&amp;rsquo;s transparency document here, as it provides a more general overview of the whole ordeal, and this article assumes you&amp;rsquo;ve read that and references screenshots from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Review: Five Star Strong Cold Brew</title>
      <link>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/fivestarstrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 23:00:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/fivestarstrong/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to write a coffee review. I have zero qualification to do so, but the fact that my blood is 75% caffeine helps.
This is going to be the first of a series of reviews on the odd coffee beverages I consume to summon enough energy to get through the workday. The subject of this review is Five Star Strong Vanilla Cold Brew.
I picked this up from my local grocery store this morning, after seeing it around for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made a Blog</title>
      <link>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/i-made-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 22:36:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ineedmore.coffee/blog/i-made-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>Yeah I made a blog. What are you going to do about it?
It&amp;rsquo;s in light mode. Why? Because it is.
Deal with it.
-eboy &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
